Preliminary Guide to the Lou Chibbaro Washington Blade senior reporter files (Washington Blade donation), 1980-2001 MS2245
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Lou Chibbaro Washington Blade senior reporter files (Washington Blade donation)
1980-2001
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2245
36.5 Linear Feet
These are the reporters notes for Washington Blade reporter Lou Chibbaro Jr. The materials date from 1980-2001.
Box R1
Box R2
Restrictions on Access
Every folder in this collection has been review by Special Collections staff. Staff have removed any documents with the designations "off the record" or "not for attribution". Any documents found with either of these designations is closed for 50 years from date of creation. If no date of creation was identified the date of donation was used. A separation form has been placed in the file and the restricted documents are currently in a parallel filing system in a restricted box.
In the case of entire interviews marked "not for attribution", the Special Collections staff may on occasion make photocopies of the original and redact the names of the individual(s) providing the information. When a patron finds a separation sheet that indicates the document was marked "not for attribution" please inquire about receiving a redacted copy. The redacted copy will then be placed in the publicly available folder.
If the "not for attribution" restriction only covered a portion of the interview then the closed portion will be treated as the "off the record" documents are treated and will remain closed for 50 years from date of creation. This will ensue the privacy of the interviewee.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Washington Blade 2008 (Accession 2008.003)
Historical or Biographical Note
First published in 1969, The Washington Blade has grown becoming the weekly news source for Washington's large and visible Gay community. The Blade has been recognized by The Society of Professional Journalists, The American Bar Association, The Washington Post, The New York Times, The D.C. Metropolitan Police Department and others, as a highly professional news organization.
Lou Chibbaro, Jr. officially joined the staff of the Blade as a full-time news reporter in 1984, but he had been writing for the Blade as a freelance writer since 1977. He has covered many beats for the Blade including the federal agencies, elections, the Supreme Court, Congress and the White House. His reporting has focused on gay civil rights, and gay rights legislation. He has also written about crime and criminal trials involving anti-gay violence and hate crimes.
Parts of this biog/hist taken from the Washington Blade website
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains the reporter records for Lou Chibbaro. The materials date from 1980-2001 with the bulk in the 1990s. The subjects covered are extremely varied and reflect the interests of the Gay and Lesbian community in Washington DC for approximately a twenty-year time span. These subjects include AIDS, political action, legal battles, celebrities, military service, hate crimes, and religion.
Collection Organization
Currently arranged in alphabetical order using the orginal folder titles supplied by the donor.
Gay men -- Washington (D.C.); Gay rights -- Washington (D.C.); Newspapers; Washington (D.C.); Gays; Journalism; Chibbaro, Lou, Jr.; Washington Blade, Inc.
- 17th Street gang attack, 1995 July 23 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- 6th and A Street, NE hostage incident, undated (Box 48, Folder 3)
- 97 Session VA Legislature, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  General Note
  File identified as reporter Bill Roundy's file.
- ABC Board visits fam bars, 1996 May 09 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- A.O. J-School Class, undated (Box 57, Folder 16)
- Accelerated Benefits, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
- ACT Up - DC, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
- ACT-UP, undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Act-up p.p. Little Rock (Clinton), undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Act up presidential project update, 1992 May 15 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Activists make appeal to closeted members of Congress, 1996 July 24 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Activists Protest PWA immigration restrictions, 1990 April 05 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Actual Stories, undated (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Addenda, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Admiral William Crowe, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Adoption amendment DC budget bill, 1996 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Adult video stores in Manassas targeted for "Gay" films (Christian Coalition), 1997 April (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Adult video stores in Northern Virginia drop "Gay" and S and M tapes, 1996 October 24 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- AGLA General, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
- AHA-HOPWA flap, 1997 September (Box 57, Folder 14)
- AIDS Action Board, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
- AIDS Action, undated (Box 59, Folder 13)
- AIDS Drug Policy, undated (Box 58, Folder 8)
- AIDS Group scandal (ARC / Gary Webb), 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- AIDS hike, undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
- AIDS home scam Montgomery Councy, MD, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
- The AIDS litigation project III a look at HIV in the Courts in the 1990s, 1996 June 24 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- AIDS lobby part II, undated (Box 44, Folder 2)
- AIDS lobby part III, undated (Box 44, Folder 3)
- AIDS Patents, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AIDS quilt - media info, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- AIDS Ride - update, 1996 October (Box 47, Folder 17)
- AIDS Training survey, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
- AIDSWalk, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Air Force and Army non-discrimination statements, undated (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Air Force Major Debra Meeks court martial, 1996 August 12 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Air Force refuses non-discrimination statement, 1997 July (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Air Force witch hunt in Hawaii update, 1996 September 16 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Al Gore, undated (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Al Gore update, 1992 March 09 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Alex. Mayor Elections, 1996 February 16 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Alexandria and Same-Sex Marriage, undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Alexandria Gay and Lesbian Community Association, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Alexandria, undated (Box 53, Folder 22)
- Alexandria, undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Amy Barnes don't ask don't tell settlement, 1996 December (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Kristina Campbell weekly files Ana Maria Rosales murder, undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
- ANC - DuPont Circle actions/agenda, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Anonymous caller 30438, 1983 May 02 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Anti-Gay academic conference Bill Kristol participates, undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Anti-gay Ads, undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
- AOL pyramid scheme, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Arlington - Partners Case, undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Arlington - Pro-gay, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Arlington County Bd Special Education, 1996 January 26 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Arlington County Board, undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Arlington County Info., undated (Box 57, Folder 15)
- Arlington County, VA, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Arlington Elections, undated (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Arlington Gay and Lesbian Alliance, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Arlington GLA Release Ratings, 1995 September 15 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Arlington GOP, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Arlington Hospital Case, undated (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Arlington police/brutality charge, 1996 January 17 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Arlington Protections clash w/ VHPA, 1996 May 24 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Arlington School Bd. Ratings, 1996 May 10 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Arlington School Board to Add Protections, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Army "plans" for gays in military hearings, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Arrest of flower vendor, 1997 December 11 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Atheists, undated (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Babbitt's boo-boo? Gay Fed. Workers, 1993 December (Box 69, Folder 10)
- Balanced Budget Amendment - AIDS, 1997 May (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Baptists, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Bar Owners, Activists Meet with Police Chief Soulsby, 1997 July 16 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Barney Frank, undated (Box 68, Folder 10)
- Barney Frank announces non-discrim. Policy for Gay Fed. Workers (including DOJ), 1994 February 04 (Box 69, Folder 16)
- Barney Frank bill to repeal sodomy clause of UCMJ, 1997 June 17 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Barry appoints to gays to constituent service posts (John Fanning / Chris Long), 1995 September (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Barry names gay advisory panel, 1995 October (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Bauer, undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
- Best Friends flap, 1992 March (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Bill bans new nude dance business, undated (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Bill Kamal firing, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Bill Roundy notes, Circa 1990-2001 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- BiNet USA The National Bisexual Network, undated (Box 52, Folder 15)
- BJ Balloons lawsuit, 1995 April (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Black Gay and Lesbian Leadership Forum, 1995 September 23 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Black gays in DC government - feature, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Blade archive access requests [1/2], undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Blade archive access requests [2/2], undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Blade Indeces, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Blade Index, 1992 January (Box 25, Folder 7)
  The documents in this folder matches the type of documents in the folders labeled Hard copies files.
- Blade Index, 1992 February (Box 26, Folder 1)
  General
- Blade Index, 1992 March (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Blade Index, 1992 April (Box 26, Folder 3)
  The documents in this folder matches the type of documents in the folders labeled Hard copies files
- Blade Index, 1992 May (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Blade Index, 1992 June (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Blade Index, 1992 July (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Blade Index, 1992 August (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Blade Index, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Blade Index, 1989 issues (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Blade receives ABA silver gavel award, 1995 August 08 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Blank forms, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
- Blood Policy, undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
- Bob Kerrey, undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Bob Kunst/FEC ruling, 1992 July (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Brian Bond named new head of victory fund, 1997 January (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Bridge Builders, undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
- British gay spy master, undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Buddhists, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Buffalo trip, 1984 August 25 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Bush-Quayle documents, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- C. Sparrow, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
- CA Murders, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
- Calendar, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  File of Lyn Stoesen, archivist.
- Calvin Deyver, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Camp Sister Spirit, undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Campaign and election information, undated (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Campaign finance: Carol Schwartz, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Campaign finance: Marion Barry, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Campaign finance: Marion Barry, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- "Campaign" GOP poll - gays in military, undated (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Canada Parents - Seek Same-Sex Birth Certificate, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Capital Area Republicans log cabin club, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Capitol Hill Scandal (pages), 1982 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Capt. Craig Button missing Air Force pilot, undated (Box 68, Folder 16)
- Casey Donovan, undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Catania, Graham, McLarty Nov. election, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Catholics (Dignity), undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
- CDC sidesteps AIDS defintion and health worker guidelines, undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Character References, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Charles Nearn - expelled from Schwartz House, undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Chef's Best, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Cherry Jubilee, undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Christians (generic), undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Christopher A. Marquette, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Chrysler, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Church Arson Prevention Act 35217 MCC comments, 1996 June (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Civ. Serv. Reform Act of 1978; Gay Fed Workers, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Clayce Rodamer case, undated (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Clinton - Brown gay marriage, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Clinton action on gays in the military (gay response, lobbying), 1993 January 26 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Clinton Admin. - Shake-up Staff Changes, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Clinton and San Francisco trip, 1996 June 07 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Clinton Appointees, undated (Box 68, Folder 15)
- Clinton flap Walt Whitman Clinic, undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Clinton issues Pride Day message, 1997 June 25 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Clinton Meets 5 Gay Leaders in White House, 1996 April 03 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Clinton Meets Gay Leaders in White House, 1997 July 22 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Clinton press conference, 1993 March 23 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Clinton remark on Boy Scouts, 08/1992, 1992 August (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Clinton "report card" interviews, undated (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Clinton "review" for two years in office, 1995 January (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Clinton "plan" for protecting Gay Federal Workers, 1993 December (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Clinton signs executive order on security clearances, 1995 August 03 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Clinton transition document - gay rights bill, undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Clinton Withdraws Judge Nominee - Responds to Opposition on Pro-Gay Decision, 1995 January 21 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- Club Bath - gloryhole closing, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Coalition of black lesbians and gay men, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Coming and Goings, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
- Commerce Dept. issues non-discrimination statement (released publically), 1994 March (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Computer bulletin board, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Congress considers restrictions on DC Gay adoptions, domestic partners, 1995 September (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Congress misc, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Congress Restricts D.C. Home Rule, 1997 August (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Congressional Districts, undated (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Congressional elections, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Contract with America, undated (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Conventions - Blade clippings, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Court Materials, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Coyle proposal - National Gay march on DC, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Crae Pridgen/Marines trial, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Cunanan material, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Dale Smith investigation, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- David Clarenbach, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
- David Schauer / FBI probes, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- DC Advisory neighborhood commissioners, 1994-1995 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- D.C. AIDS budget cuts, 1997 January 29 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- DC AIDStalk, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
- DC Appeals court approves gay couple adoptions, 1995 July (Box 8, Folder 12)
- DC Appropriations conference committee deliberates open anti-gay amendment, 1995 November (Box 43, Folder 9)
- DC Board of Elections, Democratic Leadership Council, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- DC Board of Elections, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- DC control board school authority, undated (Box 42, Folder 14)
- DC Caucus of Gay and Lesbian Democratic offcials, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
- DC "City Manager" control bd. Update, 1998 January (Box 70, Folder 10)
- DC Council actions, 1995-1997 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- DC council defeats sodomy repeal, 1992 December 01 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- DC Council elections, undated (Box 45, Folder 2)
- DC Democratic caucuses, 1992 February 08 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- DC Democratic Primary (and republican primary), 1992 September (Box 18, Folder 17)
- DC election preview, 1992 September (Box 14, Folder 7)
- DC election update items, undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
- DC Election, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- DC Gays/presidential primary, undated (Box 48, Folder 10)
- DC general election, 1998 November 3 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- DC HIV testing problems, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
- DC Judge denies joint adoption for gay couple, 05/1994, 1994 May (Box 45, Folder 8)
- DC Police crackdown on nightclubs, undated (Box 68, Folder 18)
- DC Lesbian and Gay Anti-Violence Project, undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
- DC Mayoral, Council elections - primary, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- DC Mayoral election Nov. general election, undated (Box 70, Folder 11)
- DC Nov. elections, undated (Box 70, Folder 2)
- DC Police crime report form, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
- DC Press shield law free flow of information Act, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- DC Primary, 1998 September (Box 48, Folder 12)
- DC Primary, 1998 September (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Deaf Gays, undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Deer Park Lodge vandalism of cars, 1989 February (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Defense of Marriage Act, undated (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Delta Airlines employment discrimination chargers, 1992 March (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Delta Lambda Phi, undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Democratic Convention - press info, logistics, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Democratic Convention Info., undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Democratic Party state officers, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Democratic platform hearing - Cleveland, OH, 1992 May 18 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Democratic draft platform, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Democratic Presidential candidates - campaign literature, undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Dept. of Veterans Affairs, Postal Service ban employment discrim. against Gays, 1995 August (Box 69, Folder 8)
- DHS says AIDS budget to be cut, 1995 February (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Digital queers, undated (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Dignity 25th Anniversary, 1997 September 20 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- Dixon transition report on AIDS, 1990 December (Box 16, Folder 10)
- DNC meetings, 1996 February 16-18 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- DNC roster (including openly Gay members), 1995 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- DOD bill - Gay - AIDS issues May developments, undated (Box 43, Folder 18)
- DOD experimental AIDS trials program moved to Thailand, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
- DOD lacks GLOBE, non-discrim. Policy, 1996 March 28 (Box 69, Folder 18)
- DOE, Labor issue secual orientation policies, 1994 June (Box 69, Folder 15)
- DOMA hearing - Senate Judiciary Committee, 1996 July 11 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Domestic partners covered in Fed. Worker leave policy; Gay Fed. Workers, 1994 December (Box 69, Folder 13)
- Donna Jackson comes out (Lesbian cmes out at Ft. Ord) military, 1991 January (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Dornan amendment to discharge HIV service members, undated (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Dornan staffer comes out, 1997 May (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Dr. Larry Bruni eviction from office, 1995 May (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dr. Laura, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
- Dr. Laura, undated (Box 59, Folder 11)
- Draft Plan to Restructure D.C. Human Rights Office, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Duane Beach flap in snow, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Dull gay professionals, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- DuPont Circle ANC, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Dupont, undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
- Ed Hassell, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Eddie Levine heart transplant, 1995 July (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Edited, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Editorial summit - follow up assignment, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Eduardo Burkhart - deaf gay candidate fo DC shadow senate (interview), undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
- El Faro "Car" robbery, 1993 March 27 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Election results DC Primary, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Election update "this week", undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Election update, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Electoral college background, process, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Ellen, undated (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Elvis Gene DePriest vs. Commonwealth of Virginia, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- ENDA bill update, 1996 March (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Episcopalians, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Equifax insurance investigation, undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Eric Hampton Dance, undated (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Eric Monaghan case, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Eric Monaghan trial court documents, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Ernie Smith arrest, 1992 August 01 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Escape from pick-up murder attempt, 1997 June (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Escondale mugging, 1995 December 25 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Jack Evans "prostitution" bill bans sex in DC Evans embarrassed, changes wording, 1995 July (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Events, schedules - Democratic Convention, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- [Events], undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Events/future calendar entries, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
  Lyn Stoesen, archivist, file
- Ever Conf., undated (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Exit polls, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
- F.A.C.E., undated (Box 63, Folder 15)
- Fairfax Discrimination, undated (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Fairfax Election, undated (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Fairfax libraries misc, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Fairfax libraries, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Fairfax, Arlington, Alexandria elections, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Falls Church house vandalized, 1995 August (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Family values group wants DC building for TV station, 1995 January (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Fanning - Mosely Ombudsman office, undated (Box 48, Folder 9)
- FBI / Charles Johnson case, 1982 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- FBI Brad Garrett profile, 1997 June (Box 48, Folder 19)
- FBI files / mattachine, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
- FBI files/possible gay surveillance, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- FBI hate crimes report, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
- FBI Investigations into gay hustling scene, 1982-1983 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- FEC reports from HRC, Victory Fund, and Lesbian PAC, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Fed, DC workers Life insurance open enrollment, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Fed. Maritime Commission approves non-discrim. Policy, Gay Fed. Workers, undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Federal agencies sexual orientation policies, Gay Fed. Workers, 1997 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Firehouse closings - DuPont Circle, undated (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Fitzgerald conference, undated (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Flap over Clinton executive order, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
- FOIA Requests to DCRA and MPD, 1997 April 28 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- For 3rd Year, VA Bills Flop, 1996 February 16 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- For Better of For Worse, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- For Florida story, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Fraternal insurance law, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Freedom of Information Act panel - DC, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Freeh memo - gay FBI employees/non-discrimination, 1996 November 06 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Friendly models - stables raids/FBI investigations, undated (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Fulwood flap, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Fulwood's order on sodomy enforcement, 1992 August (Box 16, Folder 6)
- GAA Bond bill, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Galen Davis (aka Courtney Chandler) police harrassment, 1995 October 13 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Gallaudet, undated (Box 65, Folder 9)
- GAO survey/marriage related laws, 1997 February (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Gary Webb/AIDS resource center (scandal), 1984 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Gay and Lesbian Democrats of America, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Gay Arab-Israeli summit, undated (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Gay Asians, undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Gay bar - gay business ownership info, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Gay bashing gang Dupont Circle and Frederick Md?, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- [Gay and Bisexual Men's Television Viewing Patterns], 2000 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- Gay clause deleted from earthquake relief, 1995 April (Box 8, Folder 4)